Guide to the Ernst Weber Collection RG.033
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Writings, 13246
  - Subseries G: Notes, 14242
    Folders with names in quotations were pre-arranged and labeled folders that kept their original name and internal order. The following folders were labeled, but were empty:
    Notes 2c was named "Permanent Magnets" Notes 3a was named "Modulation" Notes 3c was named "Demodulation Detection" Notes 7 was named "Graphical Methods: Non-linear Designs - 7"
    The following folders with illegible names were labeled according to documents in the folder, but were kept in original order:
    D-C Transient Response of Single Energy Non-Linear Circuits- 2 Applications of Integral Equations to the Solution of Nonlinear Electric Circuit Problems 14a Derivation of a Linearized Solution of the Duffing Equation by the Complex Convolution Method
    - "Types of Non-Linearity Basic, General - 1", 1949-1953; 14243 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "Nonlinear Problems - 1", 1942; 14244 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "DC Transient Response of Single Energy Non-Linear Circuits - 2", 1952-1954; 14245 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Single Energy DC Diode Circuits - 2a", undated; 14246 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "W7 DC Transient Phenomena in Non-Linear Circuits- Theoretical Investigation of Magnetic Saturation - 2b", 1931-1938; 14247 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "Non-Linear Single Energy CTS with Small Signal A-C Voltage Applied (or Small Non-Linearity) - 3", 1943; 14248 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Amplification Class A + B - 3b", 1950; 14249 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Exponential Fourier Series: Amplifier Audio Fouriers (Electronic) - 4a", 1932 - 1936; 1950-1951; 14250 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "Inrush Currents in Transformers Large Signal AC - 5d", 1951; 14251 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "Numerical Methods: Non-Linear Problems - 6", undated; 14252 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "Graphical Methods: Non-Linear Analysis - 7", 1933; 14253 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Untitled - 7a, undated; 14254 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "General Discussion First Order Diff. Equ. Singularities and Char. - 8", undated; 14255 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "Instability in Single Energy CTS (Arc) Sweep Circuit - 8a", undated; 14256 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "W107 Circuits with Trine-Varying Parameters (Linear) - 10", 1931-1932, 1936, 1950; 14257 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "Double Energy-Nonlinear Oscillations (Direct Solution) - 11", undated; 14258 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Energy Circuits, Free Oscill. - Topology - 12", undated; 14259 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - "Oscillators Feedback (Harmonic) - 12a", undated; 14260 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Oscillators, Nonlinear (Inductance, Capacitance) - 12b", undated; 14261 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - "... Nonlinear Oscillations Negative Resistance - 12c", undated; 14262 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - "Forced Oscillations: Differing, General, Existence of Periodic Solutions - 13", undated; 14263 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - "W20 Ferro-Resonance 'Non-Linear Resonance' Double Energy CTS - 12a", undated; 14264 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - "Topology Phase Space: Non Linear Circuits - 13b", undated; 14265 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - "Transients Kryloft - Bogobiuboft - 14a", undated; 14266 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Applications of Integral Equations to the Solution of Nonlinear Electric Circuit Problems - 14a, undated; 14267 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - "Method of Isoclines Lienard Construction Acceleration Plane - 14b", undated; 14268 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - "Relaxation Oscillations - 15", undated; 14269 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - "Multivibrator -15a", undated; 14270 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - "Flip-Flop - 15e", 1951-1952; 14271 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - "W104 Subharmonic Resonance - 16", 1936-1952; 14272 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - "Hill's Equation (for stability) Mathien - 17", 1943, 1951-1952; 14273 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - "Singular Perturbation Problems - 18", 1946; 14274 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - "Stability Criteria General - 19", 1937, 1944, 1950-1951; 14275 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - "Laplace Transform of Nonlinear Analysis", 1953-1956; 14276 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - "Complex Convolution Applied to Nonlinear Analysis (Differing Equations)", undated; 14277 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - "Conformal Spherdidal Loord: And Function Systems", 1944; 14278 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - "Vallise Notes", undated; 14279 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - "Additional Reference Material", 1949; 14280 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Derivation of a Linearized Solution of the Duffing Equation by the Complex Convolution Method, 1959; 14281 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Notes on philosophy, 1972-1973, 1979, 1983-1985; 14282 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Notes on equations, 1936-1985; 14283 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Notes on equations, undated; 14284 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Complex Convolution", 1956; 14285 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Notes for Thomas T. Goldsmith's 75th Birthday, 1984-1985; 14286 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sonya Weber Bio Notes, undated; 14287 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Dr. Weber", 1979-1982; 14288 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Notes on Engineering Lecture Series, 1950; 14289 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Metamorphic and Periodic Fetuses, undated; 14290 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - MIT Interdisciplinary Graduate Study Notes, undated; 14291 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Weber's calendar, 1959; 14292 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Notes on evolution, 1977-1985; 14293 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "System Science" Notes and Negatives, 1963; 14294 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "Fourier Integral Application to Circuit Theory", undated; 14295 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "Four Pole Filter Transients", undated; 14296 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated; 14297 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1965-1987; 14298 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Series III: Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 14299
  - Subseries A: Weber Inauguration as President, 14300
    - Inauguration/Dedication programs, 1958; 14301 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration press releases, 1958; 14302 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Inauguration of Ernst Weber - Rear Admiral Rickover speech, 1958; 14307 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Inaugural Address of Ernst Weber, 1958; 14308 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Dedication/Inauguration Committee memos, 1957-1958; 14309 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Dedication/Inauguration Committee planning materials, 1957-1958; 14310 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Dedication/Inauguration working materials, Alice Woller, 1958; 14311 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Dedication/Inauguration invitations, 1958; 14312 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Inauguration congratulatory messages, 1958; 14313 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Inauguration correspondence, 1958; 14314 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Inauguration telegrams, 1958; 14315 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Inauguration acknowledgements from universities, 1958; 14316 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Inauguration acknowledgement from Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1958; 14317 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Subseries B: Convocation Honoring Weber, 14303
    - Convocation planning, 1970; 14318 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Weber emeritus announcement, 1970; 14319 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Weber convocation invitations, 1970; 14320 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Weber convocation, "Scientist as Politician", 1970; 14321 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Convocation program, 1970; 14322 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - A Bibliography for The Continuing Dialogue Convocation Honoring Dr. Ernst Weber, 1970; 14323 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Subseries C: Correspondence, 14304
    - Babbott, Frank, 1964; 14324 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Brakeley John Price Jones, Inc., 1988; 14325 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1959, 14326 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1965, 14327 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967, 14328 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969, 14329 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1975, 14330 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1991, 14331 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Inter-Office Correspondence and Memoranda, 14305
    - Inter-Office correspondence to departments, 1953-1971; 14332 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Memos to faculty and students, 1960-1970; 14333 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Memos to the corporation, 1971; 14334 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1956-1957, 14335 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1961-1968, 14336 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1969, 14337 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1970-1985, 14338 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subseries E: MRI and Weber Research Institute, 14306
    - "Microwave Research Institute, 1952-1964", 14339 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "Microwave Research Institute, 1958-1965", 14340 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - MRI Research reports, 1953-1956, 14341 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - MRI Research reports, 1960-1964, 14342 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - MRI Research reports, undated, 14343 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - "Microwave Power Measurement", 1954; 14344 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Memoirs of the faculty of science and engineering Waseda University, Tokyo, 1958; 14345 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - MRI memos, 1953-1967; 14346 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - MRI Symposia, 1952-1959, 14347 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - MRI Symposia, 1960-1965, 14348 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - "Historical Notes on Microwaves", 1954; 14349 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Weber course notes on Non-Linear Systems, 1954; 14350 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Microwave notes, 1965; 14351 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - History of the Microwave Research Institute, 1985; 14352 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - MRI Patents U.S. binder, 1950-1957; 14353 (Box 10, Item 1)
    - MRI Patents Foreign binder, 1945-1956; 14354 (Box 10, Item 2)
    - Dedication of the Weber Research Institute, 1985-1986; 14357 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Weber Research Institute Advisory Council, 1988-1990; 14358 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MRI monographs volumes 1-24, 1952-1976; 14355 (Volume 1-24)
  - Subseries F: Academic Departments, Programs, and Research, 14356
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Annual Reports, 1952-1958; 14359 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. publications, 1955; 14360 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. Inc., 1942-1958, 14361 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. Inc., 1958-1965, 14362 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. Inc., 1973-1975, 14363 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Department of Chemistry, undated; 14364 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Sandia Corporation Project Report, 1955-1957; 14365 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Sandia Corporation Project Report, 1959-1962; 14366 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Ray-O-Vac Company Fellowship Reports, 1956-1959; 14368 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Ray-O-Vac Company Fellowship Reports, 1959-1962; 14367 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Polymer Research Institute, 1955-1964; 14369 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Transmission Lines: Ideal Cable, 1930; 14370 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Municipal Civil Service Exam, 1949; 14371 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Final Report for OSRD Contract OEMsr-335, 1945; 14372 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Discrete System Concepts Project (NSF), 1965; 14373 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering Reprints, 1936-1966; 14374 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Optimal Stochastic Control Theory- A Short Course, 1964; 14375 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Office of Telecommunications Management, "Technological Trends in Telecommunications", 1968; 14376 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Electrical Engineering Department History, 2002; 14377 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Department of Mathematics Undergraduate Research Participation, 1965; 14378 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Department of Urban Transportation Planning, 1965-1969; 14379 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Class notes: Mechanics and Thermodynamics of real Gases (Course 0681), undated; 14380 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kurt O. Friedrichs, Mathematical Lectures of Electromagnetic Theory, 1973; 14381 (Box 11, Item 1)
    - "Rob't Seeley Electric Design", circa 1920; 14382 (Box 11, Item 2)
    - "Elec Design", circa 1940; 14383 (Box 11, Item 3)
    - Long Island Graduate Center, Aerospace Research Laboratories, 1966; 14384 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Graduate Center and Sperry Gyroscope Co., undated; 14385 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - The Science Development Program of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1964-1965; 14386 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - PIB Patent Committee, 1970-1971; 14387 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Professional Degrees Record of Activities, 1937-1948; 14388 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Final report on the L.A. Dreyfus Co. Research Project, 1948; 14389 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Progress Report of the Protein Structure Project, 1956; 14390 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Industrial Waste-Heat Recovery Methods - Final report, 1958; 14391 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - National Science Foundation Proposals for New Facilities, 1967; 14392 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - National Science Foundation Grants, 1965-1972; 14393 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Glass slides in wooden box, 14407
  - Subseries G: Budgets and Faculty/Student Data, 14408
    - "Budget Planning", 1967-1972; 14394 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Campus space analysis and costs, 1967; 14395 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Budget summary, 1968-1969; 14396 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Budget Reports, 1968-1969; 14397 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Inter-Office correspondence - Budget, 1969; 14398 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1969-1970; 14399 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1970-1971; 14400 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee and budget reports, 1971; 14401 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Financial examinations, 1968-1970; 14402 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Student enrollment and cost data, 1960-1975; 14403 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Comparative cost studies - students, 1957-1967; 14404 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Comparative research - grants, 1952-1969; 14405 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Faculty and department data, 1967-1969; 14406 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Faculty lists and bios, 1969-1971; 14409 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Faculty salaries, 1965-1970; 14410 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Organizational chart and corporation members, 1969; 14411 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic AAUP Chapter, 14412 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1967; 14413 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Weber budget notes, 1967; 14415 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Weber budget notes, 1969; 14414 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Notes on budgets and salaries, 1965-1968; 14416 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Subseries H: Press Releases and Marketing, 14417
    - Polytechnic Press Releases - Albert E. Sobel Prize, 1969-1971; 14418 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Polytechnic Press Releases - Joshua W. Sill Award, 1956-1957; 14419 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Polytechnic Press Releases - Weber, local visits, 1968; 14420 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Polytechnic Press Releases, 1957-1964; 14421 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - The Role of Polytechnic in Long Island's Future, 1956; 14422 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Polytechnic advertising campaigns, 1975-1986; 14423 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Polytechnic brochure packet, 1968; 14424 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Polytechnic departmental brochures, 1968; 14425 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - PIB visitor's folder, 1967; 14426 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic brochures, 1967-1968; 14427 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Polytechnic brochures, 1985-1987; 14428 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Subseries I: Publications, 14429
    - Annual Reports, 1931, 1971, 1975; 14430 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Report on financial statements, 1959; 14431 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - President's Report, 1963; 14432 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Gifts to the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1965-1968; 14433 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Project Rita, Annual Report, 1966; 14434 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Self-Study Report, 1976; 14435 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic Faculty News - Robert Van Valer, 1968; 14436 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Polytechnic Faculty Newsletters, 1962-1976; 14437 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Poly Men - President Ernst Weber: A Message to Poly Alumni, 1969; 14438 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic Cable, 1973-1974; 14439 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Flyers, undated; 14440 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Subseries J: Events, 14442
    - Inaugural Address of Dr. Ernst Weber, 1958; 14441 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Address at Polytechnic Alumni Dinner, 1958; 14443 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The Establishment of Polytechnic's Long Island Center for Graduate Study and Research, 1960; 14444 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Introduction of Dr. Herman F. Mark, commencement, 1965; 14445 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Student convocation, 1965; 14446 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Commencement address, 1958, 14447 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Commencement address, 1959, 14448 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Greetings to the class of 1960, 14449 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Commencement address, 1964, 14450 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Commencement address, 1969, 14451 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - "Egalitarianism or Individualism?" commencement address, 1969; 14452 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Long Island Center, undated; 14453 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Honorary degree to Charles P. Snow, 1962; 14454 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Welcoming Address, 15th Symposium, 1966; 14455 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Our Dedicated Task, undated; 14456 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - What a Civic Center Means to Brooklyn and the Nation, undated; 14457 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Speeches, 1958-1959; 14458 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Symposia, 1956-1963; 14459 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - 1973 Commencement Program with notes to Weber, 14460 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Bugliarello Inauguration, 1975; 14461 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Dedications, Benefits, and Honor Ceremonies, 1968-1984; 14463 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Subseries K: Photographs, 14464
    - Weber Inauguration and Rogers Hall Dedication, 1958; 14465 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Weber Inauguration and Rogers Hall Dedication, 1958; 14466 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Proposed Academic Tower, 1966; 14467 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Poly photographs, undated; 14469 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Poly photographs, undated; 14470 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Poly photographs, undated; 14471 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Poly negatives, undated; 14468 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Subseries L: President's Mailing List, 14472
    - President's Mailing List alphabetical, 1969 August; 14473 (Box 14, Item 1)
    - President's Mailing List sub-list, 1969 August; 14474 (Box 14, Item 2)
    - President's Mailing List alphabetical, 1970 March; 14475 (Box 14, Item 3)
    - President's Mailing List sub-list, 1970 March; 14476 (Box 14, Item 4)
    - President's Mailing List (missing cover), 1970; 14477 (Box 14, Item 5)
  - Subseries M: The Weber Collection, 14478
    Biographical / Historical
    The Weber Collection was the name given to a collection of books from Weber's personal library, which he donated to Dibner Library in 1991.
    - Weber Collection Notes, 1991; 14788 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Polytechnic University: The Weber Collection, 1991 May 31; 14480 (Box 15, Item 1)
    - The Weber Collection, 1996 October 9; 14481 (Box 15, Item 2)
    - The Weber Collection (blue binder), undated; 14482 (Box 15, Item 3)
    - The Weber Collection with book appraisal, 1991-1992; 14483 (Box 15, Item 4)
- Series IV: Mergers, 14484
  - Subseries A: SUNY, 14485
    - Chronology of a possible PIB-SUNY merger, 1966-1968; 14486 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Chronology of a possible PIB-SUNY merger, 1968-1969; 14487 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Affiliation with State University: History of events, 1968; 14488 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Budget, estimated construction costs, and SUNY notes, 1967-1968; 14489 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Dr. E. Weber" financial reports, 1968-1971; 14490 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Terman Report on The Polytechnic, 1969; 14491 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Operation SUNY, 1969; 14492 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - PIB Long Island Center report, 1970; 14493 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn: Continuance or Condemnation, A study by the Senate Finance Minority, 1971; 14494 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn: Analysis of the Financial Future, 1971; 14495 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Documents for Negotiations", 1969; 14496 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Documentary", 1967-1971; 14497 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - "E. Weber" PIB and New York State, 1967-1968; 14498 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ernst Weber - SUNY State Education Department, 1969; 14499 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Gould, Allen, Marshall, 1968-1971; 14500 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - SUNY merger notes, 1965-1969; 14501 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - SUNY merger notes, 1969; 14502 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1961-1965; 14503 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1968; 14504 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1969; 14505 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1970-1971; 14506 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Weber correspondence and notes, 1968; 14507 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - SUNY merger memos, 1967-1968; 14508 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - SUNY merger memos, 1969; 14509 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - SUNY merger memos, 1970-1971; 14510 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Corporation Reference Material", 1964; 14511 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Corp. Ad Hoc Committee", 1966-1967; 14512 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Corporation and Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1966-1971; 14513 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Planning Board, Polytechnic", 1971; 14514 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Corporation President's Folder", 1968-1969; 14515 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - PIB and SUNY merger press releases, 1967-1969; 14516 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - PIB and New York State merger proposals, 1968-1969; 14517 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Proposals of the Downstate Medical and Technological University of SUNY, 1970; 14518 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Agreements between PIB and SUNY, 1968-1970; 14519 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: NYU, 14521
    - NYU merger correspondence, 1969-1973; 14520 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - PIB Board minutes and NYU merger, 1972; 14522 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York academic plan, 1974; 14523 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "PINY Out, Polytechnic In," Polytechnic News, 1974; 14524 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - President's reports to trustees and faculty, 1975-1976; 14525 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1975; 14526 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - "Planning and Evaluating an Academic Merger and Making it Work", 1976; 14527 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - NYU school of Engineering History, 1951; 14528 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Series V: Publications, 14529
  - Subseries A: Newsletters and Advertising, 14530
    - Newsletters, 1968-1989; 14531 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - "Washington Newsletter on Adult Education", 1969; 14532 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Press releases, 1958-1971; 14533 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Bulletins, 1925, 1950, 1987-1988; 14534 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - WNEW-TV 40th anniversary, 1984; 14535 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Papers and Drafts, 14537
    - Papers on finite antennas, 1933-1949; 14536 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Papers on linear and non-linear systems, 1949-1957; 14538 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Radiation Laboratory technical report, 1946; 14539 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Information Theory Part I and Information Theory Part II by Stanford Goldman, 1951; 14540 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Current Issues in the Transfer and Transmission of Information by D.G. Fink and J.J. Lloyd, 1977-1978; 14541 (Box 18, Folder 10)